<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources translatable="false">

    <string name="app_name">Rpg Class Chooser</string>
    <string name="reset_menu_item">Reset</string>
    <string name="barbarian_class_name">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="knight_class_name">Knight</string>
    <string name="samurai_class_name">Samurai</string>
    <string name="thief_class_name">Thief</string>
    <string name="spell_blade_class_name">Spell Blade</string>
    <string name="monk_class_name">Monk</string>
    <string name="dark_knight_class_name">Dark Knight</string>
    <string name="blue_mage_class_name">Blue Mage</string>
    <string name="assassin_class_name">Assassin</string>
    <string name="pirate_class_name">Pirate</string>
    <string name="paladin_class_name">Paladin</string>
    <string name="bow_dagger_class_name">Bow and Dagger Ranger</string>
    <string name="trapper_class_name">Trapper</string>
    <string name="black_mage_class_name">Black Mage</string>
    <string name="red_mage_class_name">red Mage</string>
    <string name="summoner_class_name">Summoner</string>
    <string name="illusionist_class_name">Illusionist</string>
    <string name="gambler_class_name">Gambler</string>
    <string name="white_mage_class_name">White Mage</string>
    <string name="witch_class_name">Witch</string>
    <string name="sniper_class_name">Sniper</string>
    <string name="beast_master_class_name">Beast Master</string>
    <string name="alchemist_class_name">Alchemist</string>
    <string name="bard_dancer_class_name">Bard/Dancer</string>
    <string name="range_question">Would you rather be close to the action or fight from afar?</string>
    <string name="dmg_type_question">Do you want to deal physical or magic damage?</string>
    <string name="armor_question">What kind of armor do you want to wear?</string>
    <string name="playstyle_question">Do you want to take an active or a passive role in battle?</string>
    <string name="special_dmg_type_question">Do you want to use any magic?</string>
    <string name="special_weapon_question">Would you like to fight with a weapon or use you bare hands?</string>
    <string name="special_stealth_question">Would you rather use stealth or take a more direct approach to combat?</string>
    <string name="special_ranged_weapon_question">Would you rather a bow or a gun?</string>
    <string name="special_alignment_question">Join the dark side?</string>
    <string name="special_luck_question">Can you rely on chance?</string>
    <string name="special_magic_type_question">Is the magic you want to use elemental?(such as fire, ice, or electric)</string>
    <string name="special_summoner_question">Would you rather be able to summon creatures or have more spells?</string>
    <string name="special_support_type_question">Would you rather hinder the enemy or support your allies?</string>
    <string name="yes_button_text">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_button_text">No</string>
    <string name="close_button_text">Up Close</string>
    <string name="both_button_text">Both</string>
    <string name="afar_button_text">Afar</string>
    <string name="physical_button_text">Physical</string>
    <string name="magic_button_text">Magic</string>
    <string name="light_armor_button_text">Light</string>
    <string name="heavy_armor_button_text">Heavy</string>
    <string name="active_button_text">Active</string>
    <string name="mixed_button_text">Mixed</string>
    <string name="passive_button_text">Passive</string>
    <string name="bare_button_text">Bare</string>
    <string name="weapon_button_text">Weapon</string>
    <string name="stealth_button_text">Stealth</string>
    <string name="direct_button_text">Direct</string>
    <string name="gun_button_text">Gun</string>
    <string name="bow_button_text">Bow</string>
    <string name="summon_button_text">Summon</string>
    <string name="more_spells_button_text">More Spells</string>
    <string name="hinder_button_text">Hinder</string>
    <string name="hinder_support_button_text">Hinder and Support</string>
    <string name="support_button_text">Support</string>
    <string name="barbarian_description">You are a barbarian. Barbarians have good damage output
        but wear less armor than other classes and have almost no magic defense. They often make up for this disadvantage by boasting 
        high natural defense.Their special abilities are mostly some variation of a berserker rage where they gain increased
        damage when low on health.</string>
    <string name="knight_description">You are a knight. Knights are generally well-rounded fighters who can wear better armor
        than other classes. They can wield a variety of melee weapons and because they can also use shields, knights have good defense
        attributes. Knights are good choices if you need a tank.</string>
    <string name="samurai_description">You are a samurai. Samurai are swordsman with a lot of potential to deal damage.
        although they deal mostly physical damage, they typically have focus or ki abilities which provide energy attacks.
        they use less armor than other fighters but make up for it with higher agility stats. Some variations of samruai
        can spend money to use certain abilities.</string>
    <string name="thief_description">You are a thief. Thieves steal items, weapons, armor, and currency from 
        enemies. They have speed and dexterity and use small weapons like daggers in combat.
        Thieves can be great team players since everyone in the party can get a cut of the loot they gain.</string>
    <string name="spell_blade_description">You are a spell blade. Spell Blades are equal parts fighter and mage and come in many varieties.
        the most typical ones have magic infused weapons that deal physical alongside magic damage. Other types use conjured
        weapons that require mana and intelligence for improvement. Spell blades are often less focused in their fighting and magic stats,
        preferring versatility over any specific trait.</string>
    <string name="monk_description">You are a monk. Monks do not rely on armor or weapons to improve theirs stats, although they sometimes
        employ claws or brass knuckles.Like the samurai, monks have special energy abilities that allow them higher damage output. An advantage of
        having a monk in your party is that they are very low maintenance and grow from combat experience while being less dependent on the items you equip them with.</string>
    <string name="dark_knight_description">You are a dark knight. The dark knight is a  powerful class that can take enemies down with weapons or dark magics, but there is a catch.
        to use many of their abilities they must sacrifice the well being of either themselves or others in the party. To use a dark knight effectively you must
        aim for high health or be in the company of a dispensable ally... </string>
    <string name="blue_mage_description">You are a blue mage. Blue mages are the most resourceful magic class because they can gain any spell
        or ability by learning it from an enemy. A blue mage\'s only inherent ability is \"absorb\" or \"learn\", but from that the extent of their arsenal is limitless.</string>
    <string name="assassin_description">You are an assassin. The assassin\'s specialties are in stealth and evasion and are known for causing high damage quickly. 
        common weapon choices for the assassin are daggers, knives, or small thrown weapons like shurikens. Assassins are handy when facing well guarded enemies or enemies with
        heavy armor since many of their attacks have piercing, poison, and bleeding attributes.</string>
    <string name="pirate_description">You are pirate. The pirate is one of the less defined classes in the rpg genre but it\'s major feature is
        the ability to wield both a sword and a gun. Pirates have rougue-like stats such as high luck and dexterity and in role-playing they tend to flip-flop
        when it comes to morality. </string>
    <string name="paladin_description">You are a paladin. The paladin is the opposite of the dark knight and visa-versa. Paladin\'s are competent warriors who possess holy
        magic and buffs for allies. They are most effective against evil or undead enemies since their light magic is often a natural bane of those types. Paladins make
        great leaders since they can handle their own in combat and allies flock to them for their enhancement spells.</string>
    <string name="bow_dagger_description">You are a bow and dagger ranger. As the name suggests, their weapons of choice are a bow for ranged targets and daggers for melee.
        The bow and dagger ranger wears light armor and have high athletic traits making them mobile and good at evading enemy attacks.
        </string>
    <string name="trapper_description">You are a trapper. A trapper\'s job is to lay traps for enemies in preparation for an ambush. The traps often 
        apply status ailments making subsequent attacks from the trapper more effective. Trappers are usually more viable for team play rather than
        solo playthroughs.</string>
    <string name="black_mage_description">You are a black mage. The black mage is the standard offensive magician. Most of their spells are associated with elemental properties
        like fire, ice, or lightning. As the playthrough progresses, their spells evolve into more powerful versions of the starter ones that gain additional benefits
        such as striking multiple enemies. </string>
    <string name="red_mage_description">You are a red mage. The red mage is the jack-of-all-trades magic class. They can learn spells from any school but 
        have issues when it comes to specialization. Red mages are useful if there aren\'t many magic users in the party since they can play the role of offense and
        defense.</string>
    <string name="summoner_description">You are a summoner. A summoner\'s primary spells are summons for entities to fight for them. Necromancers fall into this category as 
        well, focusing on undead creatures while other summoners often call on demigods or more light-aligned entities. Summoners also have buffing spells that they use
        to help their summoned allies stay alive in combat.</string>
    <string name="illusionist_description">You are an illusionist. Illustionists cast spells that hinder the enemies combat performance. Common illusionist spells include
        \"blind\", \"sleep\", and \"confuse\". Illusionists don\'t hold well by themselves as they usually have little to no damage output, but in a team they can be extremely useful. </string>
    <string name="gambler_description">You are a gambler. Gamblers rely almost exclusively on luck. They can deal physical damage using unconventional weapons like throwing cards
        or use magic abilities whose resulting damage output is based on their luck attribute. Gamblers are a rare class who can fail miserably during small scraps or defeat the final boss
        in one hit.</string>
    <string name="white_mage_description">You are a white mage. Also known as priests, the white mage is the healer of the group. In addition to basic healing spells they can remove
        status ailments and provide buffs to allies such as raising their defense or attack power. Like other support classes, white mages are best suited for team play. </string>
    <string name="witch_description">You are a witch. Witches(or sometimes witch doctors or shaman) are offensive magic users. Unlike the black mage, their spells do not necessarily
        relate to elements. Many times, witches call on natural spirits, good or evil, as the source of their magic and have access to debuffing spells like \"curse\" </string>
    <string name="sniper_description">You are a sniper. Snipers hang back during battle, preferring to take enemies out from afar. They have high damage output based on their chance
        for critical hits and benefit from increased dexterity. Depending on the setting of the game, snipers can either wield bows or rifles.</string>
    <string name="beast_master_description">You are a beast master. Beast masters have natural affinities towards animals and are a package deal with an animal companion. 
        They can use bows to assist their pets in combat or whips in some cases.In addition to owning a pet, many beast masters also have taming abilities to use against
        beast-type or wild foes. </string>
    <string name="alchemist_description">You are an alchemist. Alchemists are unique in that the don\'t normally have equipped weapons. Instead, they carry around
        items which can be crafted into bombs, poisons, or potions in the midst of combat. An alchemist\'s main atrribute is intelligence, which
        allows them to craft better potions and bombs. Always keep a good stock of items when playing with an alchemist as they are useless without them. </string>
    <string name="bard_dancer_description">You are a bard or dancer. Bards and dancers are a mix between illusionists and white mages, only they use music and dancing in lieu of magic spells.
        they are not only good support characters in battle, but also have high stats in speech and diplomacy, which can be beneficial outside of combat.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_class_description">ClassDescriptionActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
